ezinemark.com 2014-12-20

# Privacy Policy - EzineMark Blog

**General**

EzineMark respects your privacy and realizes the great significance to protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you better understand the use and safeguarding of your articles you contribute to our site. This Privacy Policy also explains the way EzineMark collects, uses, and discloses personal information provided by you. 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “you” and ‘your” refers to any visitors of EzineMark.com. “We” and “our” refers to the staff of EzineMark.com. “Outside parties” refers to individuals and organizations not owned or operated by EzineMark.com.

This Privacy Policy incorporates by reference EzineMark’s Terms & Conditions and Editorial Guidelines.

**Users’ consent**

By accessing, browsing, using the website located at the URL: www.EzineMark.com or any other sites provided by EzineMark, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agreed to the terms and conditions of information collection, information usage, and other procedures in the Privacy Policy below. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not submit articles and discontinue your access or use of EzineMark.com.

**  
Collection of Information**

EzineMark requires that you must provide certain personal information including your name, phone number, e-mail when you register as a user or access certain materials. Such kind of certain personal information helps us keep contact with you and provide you with additional information about our services and internal purposes.

**  
Sharing**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our authorized partners, but we do not provide or sell any information linked to personal information that can identify any individual person to outside parties.   
We may share information with third parties in limited circumstances when complying with legal process, establishing or exercising our legal rights or defending against legal claims, ensuring the security of our network and service, and preventing suspected fraud or imminent harm.

**User Tracking**

EzineMark implements a user tracking feature to monitor visitors’ activities. This is done regardless of whether the visitor has registered on the Site or is visiting the Site anonymously. However, if you do not register on this Site or fill in your personal details on any forms, you do remain anonymous and we do not discover your identity. If you do register on this Site, our use of user tracking enables us to identify your future and prior activity on the Site, including your activity before you registered. This includes pages on our Site that you visited. User tracking also allows us to determine through which means you have reached our Site (i.e. which search engines or links) up to one web page back. The purpose of our user tracking is to analyze our visitors' actions in order to improve the user experience of visitors to our Site, as well as to better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes.

**Use of Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small text file transferred by a Web Site to a computer that is browsing the Web Site. Even if you do not register on this Site, upon your first visit to this Site (or subsequent visits if you delete the cookie), a cookie is stored on your computer, which automatically identifies you to the Site. This is done for several technical reasons, including enabling the "User Tracking" described above. In addition, for your convenience, the cookie can "autofill" information on forms on the Site, removing the need for you to fill out the same information on our registration forms each time you want to access information that requires registration. However, cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user; the only personal information we learn about you is that which you provide to us, as described above. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. In addition, you can delete any cookies that have already been placed on your computer.

**Internet Protocol Addresses**

We collect the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site. We use your IP address in order to administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and for the "User Tracking" described above.

**Hyperlinks**

This Site contains hyperlinks to other web sites. Privacy Policy applies only to this Site and not to any other sites, including sites accessed by hyperlink from this Site. EzineMark has no responsibility, liability for, or control over those other web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, nor has it any control over, the privacy policies of any of these sites. When you leave our Site, including by linking from the Site to another site, you should read the privacy policy, if any, provided by such site.  
The applicable law and exclusive jurisdiction for settling any disputes in connection with the use of the Site shall be the laws and jurisdiction of the USA according to the provisions of the then policy in effect.

EzineMark will accumulate and process your personal information in the USA or, from time to time, in other locations at it's discretion in order to provide you with competent and effective service.

In order to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, EzineMark applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, EzineMark cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

**Policy Changes**

EzineMark reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time, even without notice, by posting another new one at the original location. You are recommended to check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes.

**Your Choice**

You can decline to submit personal information for any of our services, in which case EzineMark.com may not be able to provide services to you.

**Contacting this Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement and the practices of site, please contact us by email: [contact@ezinemark.com](http://ezinemark.com/contactus/)
